flippaisa.com 2017-06-14

# FlipPaisa: Privacy Policy

##### **_Privacy & Cookies Policy_** __

FlipPaisa.com and FlipPaisa.in(“website”, “our website”, “site”) is operated by FlipPaisa (“We”, “Our”, “Company”).

**What information do we store**

To complete your registration with us, the only personal information we ask you to provide is your email address and your name. We will never display your email address on this site, or on any other, or pass on personal information to a third party without your explicit permission.

We may request further personal information from you on occasion in order for us to provide our high level of customer service. All this data is stored securely and we will never pass any of this information on to third parties, unless you specifically ask us to or as required by law.

**Use of Third Parties**

We contract with third parties to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. Such third parties are not permitted to sell or share your personally identifiable information as part of this process.

**The use of Email**

In order to keep you informed of your activities on www.FlipPaisa.com we occasionally send you emails. These include your transaction emails to show how much you have earned, referral emails that show you how much you have earned from referrals, payment confirmations for payments to you and, important administrative emails and emails to confirm your activities on the website. These emails are not shared with anyone else apart from you.

**Your FlipPaisa Account**

A user should contact FlipPaisa from his/her own contact details; which were submitted into your profile section at FlipPaisa; in order to any change, support, update your FlipPaisa account. We may decline your request, if you try to contact us using any other E-mail or Phone No.

**The use of Cookies and Cookie Policy**

**Cookies on[www.FlipPaisa.com](http://www.flippaisa.com/)**

**What is a Cookie?**

A cookie is a piece of information which a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer. The browser saves the information and sends it back to the website server whenever the browser returns to the website.

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain (internet location) from which the cookie has come, the "lifetime" of the cookie (i.e. when does it expire), and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

Two types of cookies are used on this website:

  1. **Session cookies** which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site.
  2. **Persistent cookies** which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

Cookies can help websites to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly and are used by many major websites. We use session cookies
